statisticshowto.com 2019-05-22

# Privacy policy - Statistics How To

**Privacy Policy / Cookie Policy for www.statisticshowto.com** and the Statistics How To app

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy and cookie policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

At www.statisticshowto.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www,statisticshowto.com and how it is used.

**Affiliates**  
We do partner with affiliates, and may link to certain products or services for which we receive a commission. However, **we only link to products that we have personally used and recommend.**

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.statisticshowto.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
**www.statisticshowto.com does not use cookies.** However, our third-party advertisers _do_ use them. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.statisticshowto.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.statisticshowto.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

To view how your information is used, visit:  
policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.statisticshowto.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.statisticshowto.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.statisticshowto.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

\------------------------------------------------------------------------------ 

**Need help with a homework or test question?** With [Chegg Study](https://prf.hn/click/camref:1100l4rEQ/creativeref:1011l32299), you can get step-by-step solutions to your questions from an expert in the field. Your first 30 minutes with a Chegg tutor is free! 

[_Statistical concepts explained visually_](https://www.datasciencecentral.com/page/search?q=in+one+picture) \- Includes many concepts such as sample size, hypothesis tests, or logistic regression, explained by [Stephanie Glen](https://www.datasciencecentral.com/profile/StephanieGlen), founder of StatisticsHowTo. 

**Comments? Need to post a correction?** Please post a comment on our [_Facebook page_](https://www.facebook.com/statisticshowto/).
